The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Open !
This is...
a portal to the original body through the Sect Formation ?!
The two bodies can reunite anytime !
Master, I object !
You clearly don't trust me !
Yeah, you're right.
Master...
2 months later
Wang Lin's avatar\N8th layer of Qi Condensation
Why did it blow up again ?
That's the fifth time in 2 months.
Will this ever work ?
Without good enough control over the Earth Fire,
the pill furnace explodes.
And the pill is also ruined.
Refining pills really is difficult.
Master, I think we should
just forget about it.
It blew up 5 times in 2 months !
Why are you making it hard for yourself ?
If you continue, I will feed you to the Ji Realm.
Master,
I'm afraid this ordeal will delay your cultivation.
Didn't your teacher tell you
to consult your Grandteacher ?
Why don't you go ask her ?
I don't like relying on others.
I prefer learning.
This will definitely succeed !
This guy will probably become
the first disciple of the Cloud Sky Sect
to be expelled for destroying pill furnaces.
Senior Brother !
I made some pills yesterday.
They're good.
Junior Sister,
where are you going ?
The Southern Courtyard.
Senior Brother,
do you know the direction of the Southern Courtyard ?
It's you !
You're an inner disciple,
why didn't you get a Spirit Beast ?
Junior Sister, Teacher is waiting for you.
On my way.
The more I look at her, the prettier she is.
Cheng Xian\NEarly stage Foundation Establishment
Junior Brother,
do you know Junior Sister Cheng Ling ?
Junior doesn't like to be touched,
don't worry.
Junior Brother,
what's your name ?
I'm a disciple of the Southern Courtyard.
I saw that you were looking for directions,
I'll take you there.
I'm Wang Lin.
My name is Cheng Xian.
I remember now,
you entered the sect 2 months ago
as the disciple of Master Zhou Lin.
You're so lucky.
Do you know how many people in the sect dream
of becoming Zhou Lin's disciple ?
Why ?
Is he that good of an alchemist ?
It has nothing to do with that.
I can tell you,
but you have to promise me that
you will introduce me to Junior Sister Cheng Ling.
What do you think ?
If you won't speak, then forget it.
Senior Brother Wang...
See ? I already called you Senior.
Just introduce me to her !
I'm really in love with her.
Do me a favor.
Okay ?
Tell me,
why do people want to be Zhou Lin's disciple  ?
Because Zhou Lin has a good teacher.
Everyone in the Cloud Sky Sect knows her,
Elder Li of the Southern Courtyard is a genius.
She is one of the three rank 5 alchemists in the Cloud Sky Sect.
But they don't know that
Elder Li used to be a disciple of the Luo River Sect in the Burning Fire Country.
Elder Li ?
There's no such thing as coincidences in this world.
Are you Wang Lin ?
That's right.
Li Muwan\NCloud Sky Sect Elder\NEarly stage Core Formation
...but he couldn't have changed his aura to this extent.
We've been apart for 200 years
and my appearance is no longer that of Ma Liang.
She cannot recognize me.
Walking off the beaten path
through heaven and earth.
Before returning to dust,
I will refine this mortal body.
The left shore is the joyous laughter
that can brighten up a thousand years of sadness.
The right shore is an eternal silence
lingering under the candlelight.
To overturn this fate,
Let's go.
I will walk against the heavens.
Where ?
I will even gather the clouds
We have some people to kill.
to illuminate the sky for you.
This voice...
Look at her...
In the past, she could barely complete a Heaven Separating Pill.
But now, she is an Elder who can make grade 5 pills.
All this sadness was not meaningless.
How many lives and deaths have passed in the blink of an eye ?
I vow to break
this chess game of fate.
What's wrong ?
Disciple's pill furnaces exploded.
They exploded ?
It must be because your spiritual energy rose too fast
so the Earth Fire is unstable.
This is a common mistake.
With some practice, you will get used to it.
Since you're a disciple of Zhou Lin,
I'll give you this pill furnace.
You can fail 100 times with it without explosions.
If after 100 tries,
you still can't control your Earth Fire
then it means you don't have the talent
and you should give up
to join the Outer Sect.
Thank you, Grandteacher. Junior will take take his leave.
Ma Liang...
How can someone have such a similar voice ?
Even if there was,
it's impossible for his facial expressions to be the same.
But if he really is him,
then why didn't his Divine Sense react at all ?
Am I overthinking ?
Junior Sister, wait a minute.
Junior Sister,
I heard from you a month ago that you were missing Dragon Mushrooms.
I searched the entire country of Chu
and finally found one on the Suishi Mountains.
Thank you Senior Brother Sun
but I have found a substitute.
I refined the pill 3 days ago.
It's not valuable but...
you should keep it for yourself.
Junior Sister,
You're not a direct disciple of the Ancestors.
The only way for you to get high level pill recipes
is by forming a cultivation pair with a direct disciple.
You and I have known each other for a long time,
don't you understand my feelings for you ?
Never mention it again.
The Ancestors have arranged our marriage already.
This matter is settled.
Junior Sister, you'd better think about it carefully.
Senior Brother, is everything alright ?
Why are you still here ?
Senior Brother,
I must take the initiative.
Let's go to the Eastern Courtyard and find Junior Sister Cheng.
Wait a minute,
I'll call us a ride
so you don't get tired.
Big Ape, Small Ape !
Your Spirit Apes are just like you,
same vibe.
Let's go, Senior Brother Wang.
In the whole Cloud Sky Sect,
I'm the only person who can use Spirit Apes as mounts.
This is water for refining pills made by my teacher.
I also use these two apes to brew spirit fruits into wine.
Brother, you're the only one
I've ever given any of this.
How do I look ?
Exactly the same.
It's her, she's here...
Help me set the stage
so that I can leave a good impression.
Were you looking for me ?
He is.
Hello Junior Sister Cheng,
I'm Cheng Xian.
I want to be friends with you.
But you're just a low-rank disciple.
Are you worthy
of being my friend ?
Junior Sister,
you just entered the sect.
If I give you guidance
you will progress rapidly.
Don't bother me.
You're just a low-rank disciple. Look at yourself !
Junior Sister,
I didn't mean anything else.
I just want to...
I just want to practice alchemy with you !
Junior Sister,
don't misunderstand !
Shut up !
She's just a low-rank alchemist...
How could her teacher have given her such a powerful artifact ?
Junior Sister, please listen to me !
How dare you...
Go to hell !
Calm down,
do you really want to kill him ?
It doesn't matter if I kill him,
Teacher won't blame me.
If this escalates, it won't benefit anyone.
If I get my hands on you again,
I won't let you go so easily.
Her temper is a little bit explosive... right ?
Take care of yourself.
I must thank you,
take this jade slip.
If you ever need my help with anything,
don't hesitate !
after 93 tries...
You finally made it
Luckily the pill furnace didn't explode.
Junior Brother !
Junior Brother,
here's the Foundation Pill recipe. Please take it.
Thank you.
Why are you so polite ?
Every time we come, you prepare spirit fruits for them.
Look how fat they got !
Come on, let's go.
Why are you in such a hurry today?
Junior Sister Cheng asked me out.
Recently, this Junior Sister
became very enthusiastic about me.
Maybe she suddenly found out that I'm the best.
Alright, I'm leaving,
I need to prepare.
Let's go !
Master,
this is a high grade pill.
With your current skill,
the success rate will be low.
You're noisy.
Look at it in a positive way,
you're just...
a step away from Foundation Establishment !
You just need one pill !
I'll congratulate you early.
Maybe this is the way.
You're catalysing the reaction !
Master always has great ideas !
Finally, I can reach Foundation Establishment.
Congratulations on reaching Foundation Establishment !
This isn't enough !
Wang Lin's avatar\NPeak Late stage Foundation Establishment
in just a few months.
You already progressed this much
It's fast, but slower than my expectations.
Master, do you smell that ?
I smell some blood.
Is this...
Big Ape ?
The wound on his belly
was obviously made by someone's hand.
Someone took his Beast Core !
It must have come here for help...
It survived all the way
but died from exhaustion.
So Cheng Xian is in danger ?
What should we do ?
Should we save him ?
Cheng Xian took care of me.
We save him.
It's not worth taking risks for Cheng Xian.
And your cultivation is limited !
Don't forget, I'm not alone.
Master, what are you doing !?
It's him !
Wang Lin was able to absorb so many Foundation Pills at once thanks to the Ancient God Tactic. A normal cultivator would have exploded by consuming this many pills at once.
I've had my share of wounds,
now I want to fight back.
Is my destiny a wall of restrictions
that's blocking all my hopes
for life ?
My flesh and blood witnessed the past,
my adversity pushed me to brave the waves.
How do you navigate through the years passing by ?
Nirvana and rebirth are no longer
out of reach.
Immortals
are obsessed with delusions of grandeur.
Renegades
seek to crush the impermanence of the heavens.
Don't tell me that I overestimate myself
and that the path to revenge leads to hell
because I don't see the harm in that.
My new body opens its eyes
and awakens from its dream.
I have overcome many trials
to get this body back.
No matter how many endless dark nights go by,
I can still see.
By sticking to this thought, I will get it done
by my own hands.
Returning to my body opened my eyes,
I need to continue my Immortal journey.
With a flick of a finger,
only my indomitable heart remains.
Life and death trials temper me, I am not afraid of losing my soul.
Even if there are countless tribulations and hardships.
Overcome this fate, smash through the obstacles,
like the descent of a god.